Are you leaving
the group?
[2 years ago]
[Alphadog's dorm]
You even
eavesdrop on me now?
Are you leaving
the group?
Lower your voice
It's not decided yet
You cowardly bastard
You shouldn't
say that to me
I know you're the one
who spread
all those dirty rumors
about me
We got here after
a hard time together
but I was the only one
who got all
the attention
I understand
how hard it was for you
You couldn't help it
to vent your anger on me
That's why
I just let it slide
But now
you're even saying that
I'm a coward?
Okay then
I won't stop you
from leaving here
But
please stay until
our next album is out
Why should I?
My throat condition
is very bad now
I'm not sure if I could
hold up on the stage
If you just leave
like this now
there will be
no next album for us
and our group
will be over
I mean
please do me a favor
for the last time
I'll kneel down
if you want me to
I heard
you lost your mind
since our group
disbanded after I left
You might think of me
as a traitor
You totally
ruined my life
Don't pretend to be nice
after all of that
It's disgusting
Oh, right
I'm glad you came today
Watch me what I'm doing
with your lover